{
  "extraDescription": "Convert common fractions to terminating decimal expansions",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{17}{4}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "4.25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{37}{8}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "4.625",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{26}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "5.2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{6}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "1.2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{33}{10}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "3.3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{21}{4}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "5.25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{17}{8}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "2.125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{17}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "3.4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{35}{8}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "4.375",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{7}{2}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "3.5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{59}{10}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "5.9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{18}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "3.6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{16}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "3.2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{53}{10}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "5.3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{21}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "4.2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{19}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "3.8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{39}{10}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "3.9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{27}{10}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "2.7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{24}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "4.8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{12}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "2.4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{19}{10}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "1.9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{7}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "1.4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{3}{4}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "0.75",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{13}{8}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "1.625",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{27}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "5.4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{3}{2}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "1.5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{49}{10}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "4.9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{22}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "4.4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{9}{2}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "4.5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{4}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "0.8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{15}{4}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "3.75",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{29}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "5.8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{7}{4}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "1.75",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{13}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "2.6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{23}{4}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "5.75",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{23}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "4.6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{9}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "1.8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{29}{10}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "2.9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{11}{2}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "5.5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{19}{4}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "4.75",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "0.25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "0.5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{11}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "2.2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{9}{4}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "2.25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{39}{8}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "4.875",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{5}{2}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "2.5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{8}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "1.6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{9}{8}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "1.125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{3}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "0.6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{14}{5}\\) to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "2.8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    }
  ]
}
